that there once was
a girl who was sewing
some seeds that then began growing
on a nearby hill that gave her her fill
of knowing that caused her great glowing
knowingness.
Did you write down the five things that
you know?
>> Is there anyone who would like to begin
sharing?
>> All right.
What do you know for sure?
Begin. What do you know for certain? I
know that there is a connection to dawn
which I cannot beyond what I can see.
>> All right. Number one. Number two.
>> Number two. I know that telepathy and
deep nonverbal communication exists
within me and some of those people and
birds to which I interact.
>> All right. Number three.
>> I know that I am.
>> All right.
Anything else?
>> Yes. I know that something is happening
with regard to manifestations of numbers
and names.
>> All right.
>> And I don't know.
>> I did not ask you what you came.
>> I do know that. I do know that. What
else do you know?
>> I know that which I have doubts of
become more transparent when interacting
with Bashar.
>> All right.
All that said, if that is what you know,
all else at this moment is supposition.
The idea is to relax the supposition
and stay in the state of your knowing
and allow whatever needs to reveal
itself to you about what you know to
simply reveal itself in whatever way
it chooses to do so. Because however it
does so will then as you know be a
reflection of that knowing state and
will not have to be guessed at for what
it is or what it represents or what it
reflects to you. When you stick simply
first and foremost with what you know
and take the guesswork out of it and do
not ponder what you don't know. You can
then be assured, you can then also know
that whatever represents itself to you,
whatever manifests to you, whatever is
reflected to you will be a product of
that knowing state even if it comes in a
form you did not expect or imagine would
happen.
to drop the expectation
sufficiently
where you can allow the knowing state to
really show you what you need to know
and by elimination
reveal what you don't need to know at
that moment will allow you greater
clarity
in every moment of your life.
Thank you. Next person to share what you
know. know next person to share what you
know.
>> I'll share.
>> All right.
>> One second has passed.
>> Okay. I know I am a talented writer.
>> All right.
>> I know I have created a wonderful
organization.
>> All right.
>> I know I have people who love me in my
life.
>> All right. I know I am a loving person.
>> All right.
>> And I know that I impact many people.
>> No.
Remember what we said about impact.
>> Can you remind me please?
>> Yes. You do impact everyone. This is
true. But remember that the idea of what
you do doesn't cause the impact. It only
reveals it.
>> All right.
>> Remember?
>> Yes.
>> All right.
>> Thank you. You all already have all the
impact you will ever have. What you do
by following your joy does not create
more impact. It reveals the impact
you're already having.
>> Then I can rephrase that to say I I know
that I have the realization.
>> Yes.
>> That
I am.
>> It is all right for you to say it the
way you said it as long as you realize
how it is meant.
>> Yes.
>> Structurally.
Stay again in those states of knowing.
All else that is not revealed in that
state does not need to be known at this
moment.
>> Even if I'm getting the reflection back
from people that I have impacted them,
does isn't that true?
>> That's a revelation of your impact.
>> Okay.
>> It is not that the thing you did caused
it. The thing you did revealed it and
they are simply reflecting the
revelation.
We are discussing the difference which
may at times seem to be a fine line but
isn't. We are discussing the difference
between falling into the illusion that
you need to do something to impact the
world and living in the realization that
you already all impact the world and
that by following your joy you are
simply uncovering and revealing that
impact as opposed to having to do
something special in order to cause the
impact. So what's being reflected to you
is simply the revelation of impact you
already have just by the very fact of
your existence.
>> Then I'll rephrase that to say that I
know that I'm following my joy.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you Bashar.
>> Who else would like to share what they
know for certain?
>> Hi Bashar.
>> And do you good day?
>> Um
after trying this experiment uh
something interesting came to me.
Everything that I thought I knew or
know, I could contradict.
>> Very good.
>> And so,
>> so what do you actually know for
certain?
>> For certain that I don't know Jack.
>> Who's that?
>> You don't know Jack either.
>> But I did not ask you what you don't
know.
>> No, I you know, um,
>> you do know at least the few things we
discussed this day, and I said you could
use them on your list if you wished to.
Do you know that you exist?
>> Maybe I'm getting too esoteric and I
probably am.
>> Maybe you are.
>> But I know.
>> Do you know that you exist?
>> Of course you do.
>> It feels like I do. I think I am.
>> You do
because if you can think you do, you do.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be able to think
that you do. Correct.
>> Do you not see the simple logic?
>> Yeah. I mean, I do at one level for
sure.
>> There is no other level here. That's the
point. And that's where you get too
esoteric. You think there are more
levels and there's more complexity than
there is. There isn't. Do you exist? Yes
or no. There is no other answer. And no
is not possible as an answer.
>> Then I'm getting way too esoteric.
>> Yes.
>> Yes. I
>> So that's another thing. You know,
>> touche.
Don't get all French with me.
>> We
>> uh Okay. I Yeah, I'm I
>> Would you like to simply take time to
make a new list?
>> Sure.
>> Attempting it from a less esoteric
place.
>> I know. I have feeling.
>> All right. You see how simple that is?
And I know I have a an experience that
I'm becoming more familiar with of this
invisibility I spoke of yesterday.
>> All right. You see, knowing statements
are simple statements. They are not
complicated. They are simple statements.
>> So maybe what it is is it's something
where I I know it for myself, but I
can't prove it to anybody else.
>> That is not a criteria,
>> right? And maybe that's what I was
thinking
>> because you can't prove anything to
anyone else anyway. Anyway, right. Okay.
>> You can't even prove you exist to anyone
else.
>> I know that's exactly that's the
discussion I had.
>> But that's not the question. I only
asked you what you knew, not what you
felt you had to prove.
>> Yep.
>> And that's very revealing.
>> I got it.
>> And now you know that about yourself.
>> Thank you.
Let us for a moment shift to the idea of
what you may call the regular questions.
We will come back to what you know
Bashar
>> and good day to you.
>> Greetings.
First thing I'm going to do is um give
you my list. I actually don't have five
things on my list.
>> Oh, what?
>> I only have three things.
>> Oh, right.
>> I know that I exist.
>> Yes.
>> I know what I observe. I know what I
feel.
>> Yes.
>> Anything else is just a detail of one of
those three.
>> That's four things.
[Laughter]
>> No, I'm just speculating that last one.
>> It's still something you know.
>> I know. I'm kidding.
>> All right.
>> Okay. Now to the question that I want to
ask.
You've mentioned the subject of time
this weekend several times
>> and I want to revisit the question that
was asked last night about the concept
of frequency and the fact that it is a
function of time.
>> Yes.
>> And I want to get into some more
technical detail about that.
>> All right. Now, I've been aware for 30
some odd years that
our experience of physical reality
is a sequential
focusing of our attention on a sequence
of different universes. If I'm
understanding correctly, very much in
the way that
>> in a sense. Yes.
>> Yeah. in the way that um motion picture
film is a sequence of still frames.
>> This is of course all still an analogy
but it will do as a representative one
with regard to the thirddimensional
space-time matrix. Yeah.
>> Okay. And I'm I am speaking specifically
of physical reality.
>> Yes, I know. And within this context, it
would mean that within the idea of
an infinitude of different universes and
different realities and different
dimensions
is the idea that when we experience
movement,
>> yes,
>> what we are actually experiencing is
instantaneous shifts from one physical
reality from one dimension to another
one that is very very close. Yes. In
structure. Yes.
>> And going through a whole series of
these just like a series of frames in a
motion picture.
>> Correct.
>> Gives the illusion of motion.
>> Yes.
>> And that that motion gives the illusion
of time.
>> Yes.
>> Because we do it at a very deliberate
pace
for the most part, especially when we
have a clock that is measuring this that
movement of the clock really establishes
the the the standard of time.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. So I'm I'm correct in my
understanding that each of these frames
of physical reality is essentially
static.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. And this gets back to the the
change and no change idea that we were
talking about earlier.
>> Yes.
>> Everything is change but there is no
change. Correct. Okay. So each of these
physical realities is static.
>> Yes.
>> And now let's bring in the idea of
frequency.
>> Yes. Frequency is vibrations per unit of
time.
>> Yes.
>> But time is the illusion of motion which
is a shifting from one dimension to the
next.
And I'm wondering exactly how frequency
relates to that shifting from one
dimension. The frequency that you create
in your consciousness when you create
the illusion of time is what determines
exactly which frames fall into the slot
that give you your sense of continuity.
Does that make sense?
>> I didn't to totally get it.
>> All right. The idea is that you create
in your consciousness the illusion of
time
by creating the concept of frequency.
>> Yeah. In doing so, once you have created
that, it then determines
which of the static
sequence of parallel realities you
actually experience as your continuity
of motion.
Because let's just say again, even
though I understand there may be
shortcomings in thirddimensional
language to express this, let's say you
choose to operate on a certain frequency
within your consciousness. Okay? By
establishing that frequency, by setting
up that illusion of time and frequency,
you might choose every third frame or
every second frame or every fifth frame
as your expression of change in space.
>> Okay? So the frequency at which you
operate determines exactly how you
experience the idea of the continuity of
motion.
Okay. Which frames are represented
in that sense?
Okay. So would a higher frequency be a
skipping of more frames?
>> Yes.
>> Okay. But in but really
there's not really a skipping of frames.
It's just not that those frames that
you're quote unquote skipping just
aren't part of that motion picture of
your of your existence.
>> Okay.
>> Now, let's get into the idea of
frequency of non-physical
beings.
>> Yes.
>> Because I understand that they also
experience or express a frequency
>> to some degree. Yes.
>> Okay. But if they are not experiencing
or not focused in physical reality.
>> Yes. And we've been talking about
frequency of of uh progression of
attention on frames in physical reality.
>> Yes.
>> Is there is
>> there are frames of non-physical reality
too.
>> Okay. So
>> they are just of a different quality.
>> Different quality. What what would
distinguish the quality that they
experience from the quality we
experience?
It would be similar to the analogy
perhaps of having double exposures in
each frame
so that you can actually focus on one
thing or another in any frame.
It's not quite so structured, not quite
so limited.
>> Okay, let me bring into the discussion
a another technological analogy. Yes.
>> Our motion picture frame is our motion
picture film is a series of frames
connected together in a sequence and you
can actually cut these.
>> Yes.
>> But we have now nonlinear editing. Yes.
An electronic thing or you can you can
put the frames together in any way you
want. Yes. Almost set it to go random
and they'll it'll pick frames.
>> Yes. And this is also a quality of the
frames in non-physical reality.
>> Okay. This is what I'm thinking. what
you're describing sounds to me like the
nonlinear editing approach.
>> So you could say physical reality is
more linearbased and non-physical
reality is more nonlinearbased even
though they're both using frames.
>> Okay. So then getting back to the
concept of frequency.
>> Yes.
>> Both physicals and non-physicals
experience or express the idea of
frequency.
>> Yes.
>> The non-physicals
at the higher frequency.
>> Yes.
I'm getting the idea that means that
they are does it mean that they are
experiencing the frames of reality at a
higher rate? It doesn't always mean that
although they can. What it really is
more like is the concept of high
definition that now exists in your
reality. There's more information per
frame that they can access.
>> Okay. And I'm getting that they can
probably look at a lot of different
frames at the same time.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. which constitutes the idea of
double exposed frames or multiply
exposed frames. Yeah. From their point
of view.
>> Okay. I was thinking more of more like a
bank of television sets. But I I see how
>> any analogy will work.
>> Okay. I gotcha. Even then, it still
implies that there's some kind of a
the fact that there's a sequentialness
to it. Yes. implies that there's kind of
a fundamental idea of time that doesn't
necessarily
or or rather
>> yes I know where you're going
>> is not rigid for the non-physicals but
more rigid for the physicals.
>> Yes. Remember that anything
aside from the one
>> must experience
some degree of what you're talking about
or it wouldn't be represented as
different from the one. Thank you. That
totally clarifies that whole thing.
>> It's just a matter of degree.
>> Yeah. Okay. And in physical reality, at
least in our physical reality at this
point in time,
>> yes,
>> our our time is highly structured and
very standardized except for people who
are wafting out of it and back into it
and that kind of That's what the idea of
the increase of your frequency is all
about is you're starting to exist in
that quasiplaner reality that is
shifting dimensionalities and gives you
more access to more information per
frame.
>> Okay. Now relating this to your
experience in your reality. Yes.
>> I understand that you move around. You
may walk from your control chair to the
doorway of your spacecraft. So you are
experiencing time also
>> to some degree. Yes. Although we have
more facility with allowing it to be
more flexible. Yes,
>> I understand. But I if you are actually
walking from your chair to the door,
that is an experience of time. And
although in the next instant you may be
down on the surface of your planet.
>> Yes.
>> And then back up two instance later.
>> Uh there is the sense of time in that
there's actual movement and you can
observe movement.
>> Yes.
>> People walking around on your planet.
>> We understand it enough to be able to
relate to your sense of time. Yes.
>> Okay. And it is a realm that we
ourselves have at least to some degree
also come up through. We were in that
sense more structured in the beginning
of our evolution than we are now.
>> Mhm. Were you ever as structured or at
least standardized in your experience of
time
as we are?
>> No.
>> Okay.
>> We were created to be less standardized
to begin with.
>> Gotcha. Okay. I believe that answers my
question in its entirety.
>> Thank you.
>> Say hi. Hi.
>> Well, we say hi. Hi to them, too.
>> All right. What about saying hi hi as
well?
>> Hi. Hi.
Thank you, Bashar.
>> Thank you.
>> That was lovely
>> for allowing us to share a portion of
our experience of life.
>> Yes, we're looking forward to more.
>> Hi, Bashar.
>> How are you? Good day.
>> Um, I just want to thank you.
>> Speak up and be bold so that all may
hear what you have to share.
>> Sorry. Um, I just want to thank you for
acting as a reflection for me.
>> We thank you for allowing us to do so.
Um I have a question about instant
manifestation.
>> Instant manifestation. Yes.
>> I know that everything instantly
manifested and all through the time
delay.
>> That's the
>> um I want
>> time delay. Remember time delay is just
an illusion.
>> Right?
>> There actually is no such thing as a
time delay.
>> Okay?
>> There is always instant manifestation
every moment. It's just that what you
instantly manifest in the next moment
may not appear to look very different
than what you were manifesting the
moment before,
but it is completely different. The way
you would then recognize that you're
always instantly manifesting is to
create the next instant manifestation to
look very different from the one before
it. That's how you'll tell you're
instantly manifesting. That's how
instant manifestation would be revealed.
But you're already instantly
manifesting. But most of you are doing
it in such a way that you're creating a
sense of flow and continuity in such a
slow change appearance that it appears
as if there's a time delay when no such
thing exists.
>> Does that make sense?
>> Yeah.
>> All right. So, where do you wish to go
with this idea from here?
>> Um, I want to
>> speak up. Speak up.
>> Sorry. Um, I wanted to create a device
or a thing that allows instant
manifestation.
>> But you are the device or thing that
creates instant manifestation.
>> I know that. But
>> you want to create a reflection, a
simolacum.
>> Yeah.
>> Of that.
>> It would be an equivalent of the
controls of the holiday.
>> You may do that if you wish. What is the
first thing your imagination tells you
as what would be the best way to
approach creating such a simolacum? Um,
it tells me to start getting rid of my
belief systems.
>> No, not getting rid of them and
transforming them.
>> Bypassing them. Yeah.
>> From what to what? Can you pick a
specific belief you have now that is not
allowing you to do this and tell us what
you would like to transform it into that
would allow you to do it?
>> It would be the simple belief that, you
know, we walk around the world and, you
know, we interact and we touch a wall
and it's there. That kind of belief,
whatever that is.
>> All right. And what kind of a belief can
you actually replace it with that would
allow you more flexibility and
malleability in the illusion of
spaceime?
>> Well, I was thinking about beliefs as
maybe like a virus. Could I program a
belief to be a virus and take out the
beliefs in the way?
>> All right, you can do that.
>> Okay. Um the the zone um neutral zone
that you were talking about, I I assume
that's a method to get that done. It is
one permission slip that takes advantage
of certain strong underlying archetypal
common energies for you all. So yes, it
might work for you as well. If you wish
to apply any specific twist to it in
your imagination, feel free to do so
because your imagination knows what it's
doing when it does that.
>> Do you do you have a practical method
you could suggest to me?
>> Was that not a practical method?
>> Yeah, it was maybe. Well, what other
practical method are you referring?
>> More in alignment with my my excitement.
Allow yourself to sit in an empty room
and besides the
room have one other object of your
choosing in that room. I would suggest
that the object be of a homogeneous
material. You understand? Not many mixed
materials,
>> okay?
>> One homogeneous thing.
As you sit in the absolutely empty room
with that homogeneous thing,
allow yourself
to view it in relatively low light.
Whatever color seems peaceful to you,
have the light behind you so you can't
see it,
but have it be bright enough just to see
the thing. And as you look at that
thing,
remember what we said about the prime
radiant. Do you?
>> No.
>> All right.
>> Sorry.
>> Imagine this first.
What your scientists call a subatomic
particle. This is just a euphemism, but
it will do for this exercise. All right.
A subatomic particle. Can you imagine
that?
>> Sort of.
>> Sort of. All right. It doesn't matter.
It's not a precise thing because as I
said, it's only a euphemism. It's only a
symbol. Whichever way you choose to
depict it will work. All right.
>> Okay.
>> All right. So, do you have the picture
of that subatomic particle?
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Now imagine that this
subatomic particle has no restrictions,
no limitations.
It can actually move at infinite speed
if it wants to. Can you imagine that?
>> Yeah.
>> If something can move at infinite speed,
that means it can be everywhere at once.
Correct.
>> Right.
>> Yes.
>> That means it could appear to be more
than one particle, couldn't it?
>> Yes.
>> All right. But you know it's the same
particle. Yes.
>> Yes.
>> All right. That is actually how reality
is structured.
All of the subatomic particles in you
are the same subatomic particle. And
they're the same subatomic particle in
every single person in the room and in
the room and on the planet and in the
universe. The same one particle. Not the
same one kind. The literally same one
particle makes up everything
by being so infinitely fast that it can
actually appear to be another particle
and another particle and another
particle next to itself at the same
time.
So the trillions upon trillions upon
trillions apparently of particles are
actually the same particle appearing
next to itself over and over and over
and over again in a geometric
relationship not unlike what you are
seeing in the holotope diagram
traces that path on a multitude of
dimensions beyond what's represented
here. But nevertheless, that's a good
slice or shadow of the idea of a higher
dimensional form that represents the
geometric path that particle is tracing
at infinite speed. And every time it
crosses itself, every time it crosses
its path, it creates the idea of another
particle.
Now having said that, the idea is that
when you sit in that empty room, aside
from that one other object, if you can
begin to imagine the particle going back
and forth between you and that object
creating all of the particles in your
body and all of the particles in that
object and begin to really start to
understand and truly comprehend,
truly viscerally ally begin to feel that
it actually is the same particle that
you are that object that that object is
you. As soon as there becomes no
difference
between you and that object, you will
achieve the state you are looking for
because you will become equal to any
other thing you call an object and there
will be no concept of blockage between
you. You can become you can pass through
up down it doesn't matter. You can in
that sense become immaterial to each
other because you recognize you are one
and the same thing at that moment and
you can trade places in any way, shape
or form you wish.
How's that as an exercise?
>> That could work.
>> Yes, it could. So, play with that and
see what happens. All right.
>> Um, yeah. I was wondering is it possible
to instead of do it that way is it
possible to contact a higher
consciousness and
>> yes of course
>> okay
>> remember what we have initially said
also is that the whole point here is to
contact your own higher consciousness as
well because if it's not part of the
equation you actually won't be able to
contact another higher consciousness. We
wish to tell you all a little secret
that we have recently begun to reveal to
many of you. You're talking to your
higher self right now,
but you are allowing us to color it for
you with our consciousness to allow you
to give yourselves permission to talk to
your higher consciousness.
You're using us as a simolacum to give
yourself permission to talk to your own
higher minds. But your higher mind is
who you're actually talking with when
you speak with us.
So go have fun. Your higher mind will be
with you. All right.
>> Thank you.
Good afternoon everyone.
>> Andrew you good day.
>> Thank you. Uh we have this kind of idea
in our civilization. It's about utopia.
It's when everything is perfect and we
were trying to build it and how it's
like your civilization doesn't look like
our civilization operates on what you
would call perfect synchronicity.
Everyone is where they need to be when
they need to be. They're interacting
with perfectly who they need to interact
with at exactly the right place at the
right time. No one tries to do anything.
Everything just happens automatically
like an automatic choreography.
We are all in perfect harmony, all in
perfect joy because the only thing that
excites us is to do what excites us. And
everything that excites us harmonizes
perfectly with everything that excites
everyone else. And we all come together
to do things and we all split apart to
do our own things exactly when we need
to.
So how we come up with this ideas, it's
not kind of
it doesn't remind anything like you was
talking about
this neutral zone and your civilization.
As each and every one of you learn to
validate the individuals that you are,
you will start to recognize that unity,
complete harmony is the product of
absolute validation of all the
individuals within the union.
So by each individual becoming more
their full self, by acting on their
passion, by going into this neutral
zone, becoming a fully balanced being,
then each individual will begin to work
in perfect harmony with every other
individual who also does the same. And
the more individuals that do that and
create that state of being will then
create a harmonious world. But you must
understand another secret about the idea
of changing your world. You actually
don't change the world. You just change
yourself
and shift yourself to a parallel earth
that is already representative of the
vibration you have changed to. The old
earth is still there. It's just that
you're not focused on it anymore.
>> Does that make sense to you?
>> Yes.
>> Does that help you?
>> Yes. Thank you.
>> And uh a small question like uh I don't
remember any experience like people
describing about um uh a lot of with
abduction and everything else. Does it
mean that I don't have any relatives
>> in other civilization?
>> It does not mean that. It just may mean
that they didn't happen that way.
>> Ah. Mhm.
>> You understand?
>> Yeah. You all have relatives in other
civilizations for a variety of reasons,
but it may not necessarily have taken
place that way.
>> Mhm.
>> All right.
>> All right. And uh another question like
uh uh in a childhood I always had this I
don't know uh memory or idea that like I
was brought here for this kind of
strange program. Uh
>> all right. Well, maybe you do have
relatives that way.
Uh yeah, it's kind of like I thought uh
maybe it's how you Yeah,
>> if there is any need for you to remember
many of these experiences and
interactions, then as your life unfolds
by following your passion, you will
automatically remember. Remember, you
will never miss an appointment that you
need to keep. The only way to miss an
appointment that you have arranged is by
worrying that you will miss the
appointment.
That's the only way to miss the
appointment. Otherwise, if you don't
worry that you'll miss the appointment,
you cannot miss the appointment. So, you
will remember everything you need to
remember, you will keep every
appointment you need to keep by just
following your passion. It's an
automatically organizing principle.
>> So, if there's anything about this you
need to remember, it will come to you in
whatever way serves you best.
>> All right.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you. Pleasant dreams.
Greetings Bashar
>> and you good day.
>> I would like you to speak about phobias.
>> Phobas.
>> Yes.
>> Specifically, why does it take the
energy away from you to give you a fear
about something that you shouldn't be
afraid of?
If you are afraid of it, it is an
indication of a belief system within
you.
Every single emotion is an indication of
a definition you believe to be true
about yourself in relation to the
circumstance.
So phobias are strong symbols of a
definition that is out of alignment with
your true self. And it is a sparkling
opportunity when you feel the fear to
use the fear as an indicator and a guide
to find out what that definitional
belief is so that in identifying it you
can transform it. But it almost always
has to do with the idea of a belief or a
definition about yourself in
relationship to something in the
circumstance or some circumstance in
your life that it symbolizes.
Does that make sense?
>> Yes. No. Maybe.
>> No.
>> Oh, all right. What about it doesn't
make sense?
>> The way that it controls my higher
consciousness
that I'm very passionate about being
somewhere else.
You mean you are afraid to be where you
are? Yes. so much that you wish you were
somewhere else.
>> That's not being passionate.
That's being anxious.
>> Okay.
So the idea again is that anytime a fear
comes up, be it the idea of what you
might call a quote unquote normal fear
or something on the level of a phobia,
it is an indication,
and I'll go further this time. It is an
indication
of a belief or a definition about
yourself
in relation to some circumstance in your
life. That's what a general fear is. An
indication of some negative belief about
yourself in relation to some
circumstance in your life. A phobia
being that it is so much more amplified
or magnified
is an indication
not only of a negative belief about
yourself in relation to some
circumstance in your life. It is also an
indication of a belief of the existence
of a negative belief
that allows you to be addicted to the
negative belief
about yourself. It's a reinforcer, an
amplifying belief that's also negative.
That's why it's a phobia. That's why it
is so highly amplified.
Does that make sense?
>> Yes.
>> So, nevertheless, still an opportunity
to ask the ultimate question in any and
all of such circumstances when they crop
up. The question being,
what would I have to believe is true
about myself
in relation to some circumstance in my
life for me to feel this way
about this thing? What does this
symbolize to me in my life?
When you start asking those kinds of
questions in a meditative quiet state
once you have neutralized the idea, you
will start getting answers about what
belief system the phobia represents. So
the first step is when you feel the
fear,
all right, be somewhere else. Back away,
neutralize it. Don't put meaning into
it. Remove the negative meaning. It's
just a situation. It's a neutral prop.
It's nothing. It means nothing at all.
Now then ask the question, what would I
have to believe is true in order to have
this fear, to have this feeling about
some circumstance in my life that this
thing represents?
When you do that from a neutrally
balanced place of meditation and you're
quiet and listen for an answer, you will
start to hear your higher mind answer
you about what the negative belief
actually is. You'll start to get a
feeling. You'll start to get a picture.
You'll start to hear something or you'll
just get a knowingness. Something will
just pop into your head or you'll feel
inspired about something. You will get
some information. But that's the
question. What do I have to believe is
true about myself in order to feel the
way I do? That's the fundamental
question.
>> Make sense?
>> Yes.
>> Does that help you?
>> Anything else?
>> No. Thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you. I'd also like to talk to the
teleconference attendees for just a
moment and let them know that if we do
have a drop out of our signal to stay
online because we will reconnect you.
So, thank you all for joining us.
Would you like to ask a question? Okay,
go ahead and sit here.
>> Hi, Bashar. It's
>> you. Good day.
>> It's wonderful to be with you again
still.
>> It is always a joy for us to interact
with each and every one of you.
>> Thanks.
I was hoping that you could answer to
identify for us what the chemtrails are
that have been happening around the
planet and whether this
>> we will not talk about chemtrails.
>> Okay,
>> that data is no longer available from
this terminal.
>> Okay. Otherwise,
um can you tell us anything of the
genetically uh the man-made genetically
manipulated virus the H1N1 swine flu
that apparently is man-made?
>> That data is no longer available from
this terminal.
>> And then otherwise,
>> are you noticing a pattern?
>> Yes.
And um well third one and uh I hope it's
not the same response but the question
of the um apparently impending
compulsory vaccination that is planned
for everyone to have
>> that data is no longer available through
this terminal.
>> Okay.
>> Do you know why?
>> No.
>> These are all negatively oriented
fearinducingbased belief systems.
Okay.
In this particular time now of our
interactions with all of you, we simply
cannot
expend frequencies and energies in those
domains.
>> So in doing so for us then they will not
exist. Remember
in the reality of the vibration that you
prefer to choose, such things simply
would not exist.
Therefore, it is pointless to discuss
things which are not a part of a reality
you say you don't prefer.
>> Great. Well, thank you.
>> Do you understand?
>> Yep, I do. That's wonderful. We know
that to many of you this may seem
simplistic, but it is actually quite
powerfully profound if you really take
the full meaning of this to heart.
So, thank you for allowing us to reflect
the idea of the preferred vibration of
the new reality back to you.
Thank you. That's very empowering. Thank
you.
Let go of the things that are not you.
Let go
of the things you don't know and don't
need to know right now. For you will
know them when you do need to know them.
As the energy on your planet
accelerates, as you allow yourself more
and more glimpses, more and more
experiences, more and more opportunities
to experience the knowing state, which
is, as we pointed out, as simple as easy
as saying, "I am."
The more you allow that knowing state to
permeate
all of your life, every situation, every
circumstance, no matter how seemingly
mundane, no matter how seemingly small,
doesn't matter.
The more you do that,
I guarantee you,
the more you will suffer when you don't
do that.
Now, if that isn't some incentive, I
don't know what is.
I do not do it to scare you. I do not
say it
to make you afraid.
We say it to let you know you are truly
free
to live in that knowing state and to
live in it freely enough
to know that you don't need to know
everything all at once.
just what you need at that moment.
We do not wish you to suffer. You do not
wish you to suffer unless you do.
But it's your choice.
You don't have to believe us.
You don't need to believe us,
but you need to decide for yourselves
what state you prefer.
And you need to decide for yourself that
it's easy to create that state. I am
the dots on the paper.
The higher airplane.
That's where you live.
In that mansion, that gorgeous,
beautiful, creative, shining, sparkling
mansion.
You do not need
to live in the squalor of beliefs that
do not serve you.
If you choose to do so,
understand that you're choosing to do
so. There are no exceptions,
but you don't need to do so.
You can be in knowing.
You can because I have just shown you.
It's as easy as I am.
As soon as you say that, as soon as you
remember that, you are in a knowing
state. There is no reason and no excuse
that says I can't create the knowing
state
because it is too simple to do.
So if you say, "I can't I can't I can't
get to the knowing state," I guarantee
you this. From this point forward, we
won't believe you.
Say it out loud. I am.
>> I am.
>> It is an absolute fact.
You didn't have to repeat that.
>> But thank you for doing so.
Shows you are in the moment
because it's true. It is an absolute
fact. If you want to say it out loud, by
all means, it's an absolute fact
>> that I am.
>> I am.
>> There is absolutely nothing that can
contradict this. Nothing exists that can
contradict this. If you are, then you
are. That's it. Isness is your only
quality. It can become nothing else.
Isness, the quality itself can become
nothing else. Yes, within creation, you
can experience becoming many things, but
all of them still exhibit isness. They
all still exist. You still exist. No
matter what you become, you still exist.
Existence is your basic quality that
can't change.
It is the first law.
It doesn't change. It is. It is. It is.
It is. It is. You are. You are. You are.
You are. I am. I am. I am. I am. I am.
Even if it were possible
for you to suddenly not exist at all,
you'd never know it. So why bother
caring?
Why spend time worrying about it?
You would never know it had happened.
But if you do exist, I guarantee because
all that is guarantees by its very
nature.
If you exist, there is only now. So you
must always exist because there is only
now.
There's only now in which to exist. And
if you exist in the only now there is,
you always will because there's only one
now. That's it. So here you are. You're
part of the club. Lifetime, lifetime,
lifetime, lifetime, lifetime to infinity
membership
free of charge
forever.
Start taking advantage of membership
privileges.
It's up to you.
Stay in your knowingness.
It's up to you. But now you know it is
simplicity itself to be in that state.
There is no rationale
whatsoever that will make sense anymore
that says that state cannot be achieved
because it is the actual easiest state
to achieve because it's the most basic
state to achieve. So start from there.
Let it be obvious and let the
obviousness filter into every aspect of
your life. And let it be all right to
not know what you don't know. That's all
it takes. That's all it takes to have
absolute serenity
in your life on every level for
everything.
Be in the now. Be in the knowing.
Do you think it's an accident that in
your language the words now and know are
so close in structure?
Be in the now and you will know. Be in
knowing and you will always be in the
now.
Always. It's that simple.
What is your time frame?
We know you enjoy conferring about time.
We will give you an opportunity to do
so.
>> You mean before the break?
>> Did that make you feel good?
Have you come to a consensus now about
the difference between time and timing?
>> I was referring to the entire session,
but I didn't We're having another break.
So, we're in agreement.
>> I see.
So, the same event produced two
different perceptions.
>> Thank you for being an illustration of
our first demonstration.
Let us take three more questions.
Bashar, this is a question from a news
for the soul listener.
>> Oh, all right.
>> And it's a compound question.
>> Compound question.
>> Yeah. I'm going to put these together.
>> Yes.
>> Says,
okay, I can talk the talk, but why is it
so hard to walk the walk concerning
faith when the chips are down and things
aren't going my way? Am I just deluding
myself? And
please explain where the line is, the
limits of what is actually possible
through the power of faith or knowing
for real in this dimension of reality.
>> To some degree, this question has
already been answered. The idea simply
is is that any delusion that exists is
the delusion that the negative belief
systems hold sway over the positive
ones. So when you say the chips are
down, turn them up because you have the
ability to do so. It's not deliluding
yourself to turn them up. But the irony
is you don't think you're deluding
yourself when you turn them down.
The idea is as we have recently
discussed also,
yes, of course you live in what might be
described as a relatively limited
reality and of course certain things
will not be
apppropo to manifest in your reality.
It doesn't mean that there really are
limits per se, but there certainly are
agreed upon parameters that will make
sense according to your local reality.
So you will usually abide by them. But
with you have free reign to go far and
wide in choosing anything that
represents your creativity and joy. To
put it simply, if there is really
something you're passionate about in
your reality, it really truly represents
your true passion in that reality. It
would make no sense for you to not be
capable of manifesting it in your
reality. Therefore, anything you're
truly passionate about, you probably
wouldn't be passionate about if it were
not possible to manifest in your
reality.
>> That sounds wonderful.
>> We think so.
>> Oh. Oh, what? We know. So,
>> Oh, that's great. Well, thanks very
much, Bashar.
>> You are welcome.
>> Any other questions?
>> Good afternoon, Bashar.
>> And are you good day? Um, when we speak
of the
common time space continuum, when you
do, you speak of it as a
three-dimensional
continuum of space and time. Time not
being treated as a fourth dimension.
>> Well, we're just using your colloquial
vernacular. We understand that from your
scientist's point of view, there are
three dimensions of space and one of
time, making you in a sense a
fourthdimensional reality. But we also
understand there are many different
kinds of terminologies that exist in
your reality about dimension and density
and it can to some degree be somewhat
confusing.
>> Understood. Einstein does refer to the
fourth dimension as an imag like an
imaginary dimension of space.
>> Yes.
>> Now understanding as I thought I had
that time and space are inseparable in
my experience.
>> Yes. I come across what they call M
theory.
>> Yes.
>> Which arrives short version at an an
11thdimensional model.
>> Yes.
>> In which they have 10-dimensional
universes.
>> Yes.
>> Floating in an ocean.
>> Of an 11th dimension of time.
>> Yes. And that sounds to me like we have
now made a new kind of time which is
absolute linear and just like the kind
of notion of time that was pre-
Einsteinian. And I'm having some desire
to put these notions of time together or
relate them.
>> I see what your scientists are actually
discovering is that there are levels to
the concept. We sort of discussed this
before when we said that anything
outside the one does create some sense
of quote unquote space-time referential
positioning. But there are varying
degrees of this. There are certain
levels of this. And what they have
simply come across is they have reached
an understanding that there is another
level above physical reality where that
kind of so-called barrier that arbitrary
barrier also exists. I'll put it another
way. We have often said and this again
may seem like an arbitrary
representation but you will understand
the analogy. We believe that above a
certain frequency level, what you call
the speed of light, that defines the
border, so to speak, of your physical
space-time reality. But there are things
that exist at higher frequencies than
that that are not part of your
dimensional experience. But even that
domain has its own upper limit beyond
which you then recognize you've shifted
to yet again another domain and another
domain and another domain and another
domain. So the theory that your
scientists are working with now is
simply a mathematical representation of
a higher domain's upper limit where it
would once again seem to be the kind of
impositional structure that is similar
to the kind of impositional structure
you experience in your typical
third-dimensional space-time reality. Is
this making any sense?
>> Oh yes.
>> All right. So it's not so much that I
need to take the physical picture as to
understand that this is an expression of
a mathematical reaching.
>> Yes.
>> Now um I have and I'm going to ask you
to critique or whatever this notion. It
is my understanding that in a continuum
of any number of dimensions it takes one
more to know it.
>> Yes. So that
>> as your Einstein said, you cannot solve
a problem from within the state of mind
that the problem was created. You cannot
see the forest for the trees. You have
to be beyond the forest to see the
forest.
>> So that if it takes 10 dimensions for
for example for all there is.
>> Yeah. Knowing that that's just an
analogy.
>> Yes.
>> All right.
>> Then I would be the 11th dimension
contemplating it objectively.
>> Yes. And that is not essentially a sound
uh way to hold the idea.
>> Yes, it is one way to begin to work with
those concepts by always understanding
that in order to perceive a concept in
its entirety, you actually so to speak
have to be beyond it, which
automatically implies a bigger reality.
Are you suggesting that the assignment
of a finite number of dimensions to all
that is is
um inappropriate?
>> It is not that is inappropriate. It is
appropriate for how you may want to work
with certain concepts. But it will never
be an accurate representation because
infinity will always trump the finite.
>> Mhm. So whatever I make of that notion
is a limitation.
>> Yes. But it may be a very plausible or
workable one for what you may need to
apply it to.
>> Thank you.
>> Hello Bashar.
>> How are you? Good day.
>> I know that I have chosen to suffer this
weekend.
>> Oh, all right. And why did you choose
that?
>> I have been experiencing a challenge to
my faith.
>> Yes. And this weekend has brought me
from despair and anger to hope.
>> And I was listening to what you've been
saying. And I'm
>> getting closer back to faith. But I was
>> Are you going beyond faith to knowing as
well?
>> No. And I was wondering if there was
anything more that you would like to
tell me to bring me to a stronger faith
and towards
>> I am not attempting to bring you to a
stronger faith. I'm attempting to bring
you beyond faith to knowing.
Did you do the I am exercise?
>> I did.
>> Do you understand that when you say I am
that that's an absolute fact?
>> I do.
>> Then you know
>> it's that simple. Did you not believe us
when we said it was that simple? Is that
part of the challenge?
>> The challenge for me is when you say
circumstances don't matter.
>> Yes. You want me to explain that?
>> I want to know how I can believe that
and demonstrate it.
>> Oh, thank you.
We often have said, though we understand
how this first sounds in your language,
we don't mean it negatively, that the
greatest gift creation has given is that
life is meaningless. There is no
built-in meaning to situations or
circumstances. They're just neutral
props. I'll put it another way. You are
aware to some degree, as we demonstrated
earlier, that any given situation can
actually produce even opposite results.
Yes.
>> Yes. or opposite perceptions. Yes.
>> Yes.
>> All right. You can look at any situation
and you could see a positive outcome or
you could see a negative outcome of the
same situation. Yes.
>> Yes.
>> Well, that shows you that no situation's
meaning is absolutely built in.
It's determined by how you see it. So,
if you decide that a situation will have
a positive effect on you, that's the
effect it will have. If you decide it
will have a negative effect on you,
that's the effect it will have. The
situation doesn't come with a builtin
parameter that says it's going to affect
you positively or negatively. That's in
your hands to determine. So nothing has
built-in meaning. And therefore, that's
why we say the circumstances don't
actually matter. It's the state of being
that matters because it's the state of
being that allows you to determine what
meaning you will assign to those
circumstances that are fundamentally
neutral.
Does that make sense?
>> But if someone's in harm's way, how can
that how can you look at that in a
positive way?
>> All right. Thank you. There is a
difference between observing that
something is mechanically negative or
mechanically positive. Positive being
segregative
in that sense. The negative being
segregative, the positive being
integrative. You understand?
>> No.
>> You don't?
>> All right. When we talk about positive
and negative, we're not talking about
subjective good and bad. We're talking
about an actual mechanical description
of energy. That which is negative in
that sense is that which segregates,
separates, shall we say, isolates,
disconnects, forms experiences of
disconnection.
That which is positive forms experiences
of integration, unification, bonding,
oneness. Do you follow that?
>> Yes.
>> All right. some examples.
>> The idea being that if you operate on a
fearbased
definitional system, more often than
not, you will experience more emotions
of disconnection and greater fear. Thus,
you are seeing that the mechanism is
simply generating an expanded version of
itself
by perpetuating more doubt, more
disconnection, more fear. Does that make
sense? more misalignment within your
belief systems from your core. The fear
itself is the expression of negatively
aligned belief systems. Does that make
sense?
>> Yes. So the idea being when you see
somebody operating in a negative way or
when you see a situation that you are
saying someone is being harmed in you
can recognize the mechanisms that might
be involved may be negatively based.
Nevertheless, you can also recognize as
you can in many situations in life that
that being that person while not
necessarily excusing the negative
behavior might also allow others to
learn something positive from it or
might give someone else a positive
effect. I'll put a very simple example
before you. We understand that it is
negative when someone abuses another
person. That's a negative act
perpetuated by negative beliefs. It is
segregative. It is isolating. It is
disruptive. It is disconnective.
Nevertheless, if you came upon the
situation where you're seeing someone
being abused and you come to their
assistance and help them, then you are
putting positive energy into it. And if
you say
in seeing this I am now inspired
passionately to do what it takes to make
sure this doesn't happen again on our
planet anywhere then you are going to
generate a positive effect out of what
essentially started as a negative
experience. Do you follow that?
>> Yes.
>> So it's how you use it and that's why we
simply say circumstances don't matter.
Not to discount them, but to let you
know it's what meaning you decide to
give them that determines what effect
you can extract from them and apply to
your reality.
Remember,
everyone that is having an experience is
fundamentally an eternal infinite
spirit. You follow me?
Ultimately, everyone
everyone is just fine.
Everyone, I'll put it colloquially,
everyone goes to heaven, no matter what
they've done because that's the only
place there is.
The idea is is that you are created in
unconditional love and that's the only
place there is to go back to
unconditional love. Now, individual
beings may learn that they didn't
necessarily want to operate in a certain
way because it may have created an
experience for them that is more
negatively oriented than positively
oriented. And they may learn to do
something about that from that
experience. That's up to them. But the
point is is that when we say
circumstances don't matter, we're simply
attempting to let you know that they are
fundamentally neutral and that you can
decide how they will actually affect
your reality. What you will do with that
experience. Just because the experience
may start negatively doesn't mean that
the only experience you can get from it
is a negative one. You can actually use
it to learn a lesson and actually create
a very positive reality from that
negative experience. Does that make
sense?
>> Yes.
>> Also, when we say circumstances don't
matter, but only states of being do, we
are making a play on words of the term
matter.
Circumstances aren't what materialize
your reality. It's your state of being
that materializes
reality experience for you. The
circumstances are simply neutral props
that allow you to decide whether you are
by reflection in alignment or not.
>> Does that help
>> very much?
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you very much.
>> Hello again, Bashar.
>> And to you, good day.
>> Um, all right. I'm curious now.
>> Oh, all right.
>> From what from what you sense right now,
>> yes.
>> Can human evolution lead to certain
super abilities becoming more real? For
example, uh radical spontaneous change
in physical form?
>> Yes.
>> Oh, okay. Flight.
>> Uh spontaneous regeneration.
>> Yes.
>> Um Okay, cool.
>> There are actually already people on
your planet, though they are not many in
number, that can already do these
things. Oh,
>> you typically call them shamans.
>> Okay, cool. Uh,
>> there's that temperature again.
>> Yeah,
>> it's very nice. Thank you very Yes.
Thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> You may all at this time take a short
break. We will resume contact with a
story.
Or it'll say let us continue this
transmission
with the following story.
Relax, become comfortable
and let us begin
in your traditional way. Once upon a
time
there
was
many of your years ago, but yet to you
still many of your years in the future.
A world
which was fashioned
for the purpose of continuing
a civilization that had brought itself
to the brink of destruction.
And this world was fashioned
so they could have a second chance at
perpetuating
their culture, their civilization.
These are the ones who made us.
The ones who made us,
found your parallel reality and other
parallel realities
and fashioned from their own genetic
material and yours.
Several
hybrid species of which we are one.
I began my incarnation in my
civilization
137 of your years ago.
But yet
still
2,700
years in your future.
as I was born in my society
and allowed to be telepathically
connected. I did not forget
my connection to my spirit, my higher
mind, my over soul in which was made
an arrangement, an agreement
wherein I would have
also what to me is a past life on your
world, which is the channel before you.
And in that arrangement
was set out certain parameters for how
that communication would occur, would
evolve.
And it was taught to me
at age three
that I would contact
my past self also at age three
and form the bridge and the link that
would connect us through this life. And
I was taught the way of doing these
things. For I knew and I remembered that
this would be my expression, my passion
to open gateways and open doorways for
the consciousnesses of those on the
threshold of new awakening and new
realities and new experiences.
And I was filled with great joy to
realize
my becoming.
And as my orbits around my central star
progressed
and I became what you know as the
seventh year of life.
Thus then was I also introduced to
another who was to be a counterpart in
this endeavor, who as a female of my
society would also be an initiator of
the opening of the gate and the opening
of the door.
And as such, I would eventually take
upon myself the Appalachian that you
have come to know as Bashar. So she
would take on the Appalachian known as
Anima. And in this way together we would
work to initiate contact and open many
doors so that those civilizations with
whom we would interact would eventually
be those who would join the alliance of
worlds.
And in this way did we grow and train
and learn and explore together.
And before my time,
there was the creation by those that
made us of a repository of knowledge on
our world. And not only upon our world,
which in our ancient language is
Eathani,
place of living light, but on all the
other worlds they had fashioned, and
also placed there upon other hybrid
races, each of whom would play a part in
a variety of ways of opening up
remembrance, contact, and continuence
with The ancestors which are you anani
in our ancient language.
The ancestors, the ancient ones who are
in that sense from whom we are made.
We are in that sense all the hybrids,
your extension and your children. But
each plays a different role in the
remembrance and rejoining of family.
We play our part in initiation.
But there are those who will be the
first to make open contact with you, who
have begun to show their ships to you,
as we have named them. Those encounters
you have come to know as the Phoenix
Lights, being representative of one such
ship of that group who shall be the
first
and are now through us allowed to
represent that as we are Ethani and you
are Anani. They are the Shaloniah
which means those who will come first.
The Shaloniah are our cousins, our
brethren, and your immediate children.
From those experiences you have labeled
abduction on your planet, which is for
the further perpetuation of the species
of those who made us, your counterpart,
humans, in a parallel reality, who have
mutated beyond the recognition of the
human form, and in so doing prevented
themselves from continuing in the same
manner as which you do through
reproduction.
But in contacting their parallel selves
of which you are parts of the same
oversoul to shall we say initiate the
idea of contact through what you have
called the abductions did form bonds
that were unexpected in their oversouls
to allow them to glean and glimmer a new
sense of emotionality and the potential
of what you can become as a parallel
reality that can take a path.
unlike the path they took.
They recognize that you are similarly
heading down the same road of
destruction, but know that for you there
is a fork that they did not take. And in
so creating the hybrid races such as
ourselves did put upon us the task of
assisting our ancestors, the Anani, to
aid and assist in waking you up as you
travel down that path. So that by the
time it comes time to arrive at that
fork in the road, you will take the one
they did not take. And you will take the
one that will allow you to continue. And
you will take the one that will allow
you to rejoin the family that they have
taken from you in perpetuating
themselves. The family that shall
return. The first of which being the
Shaoliniah.
As they return,
as they open contact, they will bring
gifts of knowledge and awareness. They
will remind you of your true histories.
Not history in the singular, but
histories all the way back to the
origins of the DNA that has plied its
way through space. Finally arriving in
the solar system you call your own, and
setting up incarnations on the planet
that has been destroyed, Marduk, on the
planet that has been destroyed, Mars. on
the planet that has yet to be seen as
whether it will live or die, the Earth,
but which we know you will continue on
with. For we would not at this point be
speaking with you had you not taken the
fork that would allow for the family
reunion.
We thank you for taking the fork. And
even though we know these are still what
you would recognize as the dark days of
confusion when it does not always seem
as if you are moving toward the light
from our perspective. The gift that you
have given to us of life allows us to
reflect our knowing back to you. That
that is the road you are on. For we are
on it with you and we will never ever
leave your side. Though we may present
ourselves in various ways at various
times and express our beingness with you
in a variety of endeavors that shall
take different forms that shall
transform
always. It will be with the essence of
ourselves left within that endeavor that
shall continue side by side with you the
Anani our ancestors.
For we thank you for the gift of life
and I thank you for my experience on my
world and on yours simultaneously.
I am enriched and we are all enriched by
each and every experience you allow us
to have of you. For we not only discover
more of ourselves
on our own world, in our own reality,
but we discover more of ourselves
through you,
through the aspects of you that are
within us as your ancestors, as your
descendants, as your children.
Fear not,
worry not.
You will become
what you desire to be.
For we see you as you are in our time
and in our time
you are among the stars
and you know who you are.
And in our time
there is another form of life on earth
learning its lessons,
creating its experiences,
but you will leave behind.
A few things they will ponder and they
will wonder about you and where you
went.
And in spirit you will guide them. Even
as in body you will explore other worlds
and assist others as we assist you.
Other star systems evolving, other
cultures evolving
and you will contact them much as we
have contacted you. And you will be
their entities
and make them wonder
what lies beyond.
And you will bring them up the ladder
with all of us
as you take your place as a full-fledged
member of the interstellar alliance.
That gathering which together
synchronistically expands, enriches
all who participate,
all who harmonize within it.
Because the core
is the freedom
to be the fullest individual
and to learn that by being such that
this
is what creates the harmony of unity.
That diversity and the strengthening of
your diversity, your true nature is what
allows for the harmony of the
unification
to express itself perfectly
and allows for continued expansion
within all that is.
We share with you our beating heart.
For it is with the unconditional love of
all that is
that we speak with you and that we
remind you
to know yourselves
fully.
One moment.
One moment. One moment. One moment. One
moment. One moment.
Look
to
your Arizona area in your year of 2010.
There shall be another opportunity
for contact
with the Shaloniah.
Look to your Arizona area in your year
of 2010.
There shall be another opportunity
for contact with the Shaoliniah.
In your year
of 2008,
you shall have
an opportunity to set in motion
the circumstances
in your society
that will allow
for the initial
recognition
to occur in 2010.
In 2012,
there shall be
in a variety of what you call sacred
sites
another opportunity
for recognition of the Shaloniah.
Five years hence
from then what you would call your year
of 2017.
There shall be
the first broad awakenings of the
memories of contact that has occurred
in and around various cities.
People will awaken to dreams that are
memories.
There will be at first psychological
confusion
at this.
But by your year of 2020,
the dreams will explain themselves
sufficiently so that all of these that
remember
will communicate with all others that
recall. And there will be the
establishment of communication
vehicles, centers, sites on your
internet
for those that remember the encounters
that will reveal themselves in the
dreams.
After your year of 2025,
there will then begin
a series of limited open contacts in
isolated areas pre-determined,
pre-selected,
pre-chosen
on your planet
in and around your year of 2030.
There will be preparations for largecale
open contact in your year of 2033.
These events are as we read your energy
now.
You have the ability in your year of
to put exactly this timeline in motion.
You also have the ability to extend this
timeline depending on what you do in
your year of 2008.
It is in your hands
now more than ever before.
Begin open dialogue.
Begin requests of open discussion of
what your government knows of
extraterrestrial existence.
strongest opportunities that exist in
for the change of your American
government.
Infuse
that change with recognition not only of
what must accelerate to aid and assist
the environment of your world but
simultaneously
with the idea of contact with higher
different other intelligence.
begin in whatever way is representative
of your passion. These dialogues, this
infusion, these ideas, use your
imagination come from the knowing you.
Do not be afraid of the dream.
Do not be afraid of the dream. Do not be
afraid of the dream.
The dream is what will awaken you.
That is the paradox.
Dare to have the dream that will awaken
you,
know yourself.
And as you know yourself and give off
more of the frequency of your true
essential nature,
the Shaoliniah shall recognize you by
that sign
and shall gravitate toward those they
must meet.
When the time comes, when the reunion
happens,
this is simply
our opportunity to share these ideas
with you, to share this possibility of
unfoldment with you.
One moment. One moment. One moment.
Mommy,
daddy,
we will soon no longer be just in your
dreams.
Mommy,
daddy,
if you will have us,
we will live side by side
on a new world
that will be both,
your
and our
home.
We will be in your dreams.
Good night, mommy. Good night, daddy. We
will see you soon.
One moment.
Your world is preparing to experience
a level of unconditional love in the
near future
unprecedented
on your planet.
Even in ancient times with other
civilizations
that were far more connected, far more
in remembrance of their connection to
spirit.
Never before on earth
have you gone through the darkness to
the light in this way. And the
remembrance
shall be profound
by having taken that path. And the love
once regenerated shall never be lost
again.
And in 1,000 of your years,
you will no longer incarnate at all as
humans on your world, but will, as we
said, leave it for others to use for
their own journeys,
their own experiences, their own
discoveries of self. But you will guide
them. You will aid them. You will be
their spirits. You will be their
entities.
You will be the ones to whom they turn
for guidance.
This is your legacy
even as it is wrapped up tightly with
ours.
For we are one family
and as family we are inseparable.
We love you
all of you. Each of you
forever and ever and ever.
doggy toy.
We are going to
remind you now to know yourselves.
Remember the simple things we have shown
you here.
The simple ways,
the I am to be in knowing,
the dot on the paper.
That's all it takes. Know what you know.
You don't need to know what you don't
know right now.
That is sufficient for you to be all you
need to be in this moment.
Enjoy yourselves as we enjoy you
once again. Take a deep breath.
Let it out.
Take another deep breath.
Let it out. and let all the anxieties
go.
No worries, no anxiousness.
Take another deep breath
and hold it and hold it and hold it.
And as you let it out, release
and say out loud, I am.
And that's all I need to be.
>> And so it is.
We will extend to each of you at this
time in perfect timing
our deepest heartfelt unconditional love
for the cocreation of this interaction.
And simply we remind you that no matter
in what form it comes,
there are more surprises ahead,
more excitement around the bend.
Your imagination is limitless.
Let it be your guide and it will always
lead you into the perfect place in the
perfect time and the perfect surprise to
discover more of your knowing self.
and we will see you
in and in between your dreams.
Our unconditional love to you and good
day.
How did it go?